肥猪网 www.fz222.com
本视频字幕由肥猪网独家呈现
小时候我就爱两样东西：
电视游戏和日本怪兽电影
哥斯拉、蛾怪、飞鸟怪、吉多拉和钢铁哥斯拉
这些怪物在那互相斗争
并且看到什么就灭什么
这感觉好极了
作为一名美国80后
当一名哥斯拉粉丝不是那么容易的一件事
因为想看到这些电影就必须等到它出CD碟
或者是在周末扫遍所有的电视台看它有没有播放
再或者去一家本地的影音店
看运气也许可以在VHS找到什么
在我的童年记忆中
只有两部哥斯拉电影在美国上映
哥斯拉1985和哥斯拉2000
美国的1998版本不算
直到我去网上查了以后才知道
东宝公司自从90年后一直都在制作这类电影
但是都只能去日本看
我气啊气啊
就算是电视游戏也很难拿到
这是我玩的第一款哥斯拉游戏
哥斯拉NES版本
我们把这块屎一样
的游戏插进游戏机口开始玩吧
哥斯X 怪物之王
可以看得出来这游戏有多么粗制滥造
因为它都遮住了一半游戏名了
公元2XXX年...
那么多X你什么意思？
无法预计准确时间就给那么多个X？
收到了一份来自于地球的通知...
去你妹的 直接玩吧
看起来不错啊
这是什么玩意？哥斯拉国际象棋？
你可以在这些六边形之间移动哥斯拉和蛾怪
然后你就去战场
这还不错嘛不是么？
传统的单向卷轴式动作
更像经典的无脑拆手柄游戏
看在有那么多攻击方式上给你个好评吧
哥斯拉拳打脚踢
兼尾巴扫击再加上嘴巴喷射线
哥斯拉什么时候去了太空观光？
我只记得一次在电影哥斯拉Vs.零怪兽
为什么不设计在地球上？
我想拆几栋楼
而不是拆这些破石头
哥斯拉跳跃不用弯下自己的脚？
看起来它像站在跳跳杆上跳来跳去
这是什么？邪恶图腾杆？
这是什么？那是什么？
这些都是些什么鬼东西？
哥斯拉被送到了什么
堆满宇宙垃圾的星球吗？
全部都是些见都没见到过的东西
过了几个回合Boss会自己移动几个格子Then we return to the track and the machine enters the monsters.
然后到了你的回合
你可以选择移动哥斯拉或者蛾怪
我们来玩玩蛾怪吧
好消息是它可以飞上天
就是说你可以避过那些障碍物
玩哥斯拉的时候
每两秒钟就会有一块石头挡住你的去路
蛾怪就直接飞过那些屎一样的石头除非你被攻击了
每次被打到就会掉到地面去
它可以喷土豆和丢翅膀下地
没错丢翅膀
就像丢自己的手臂一样不科学
蛾怪很垃圾
就只有这两种攻击方式 被人笑话弱爆了
这是什么？什么东西打了我？
什么？难不成是这火山？
我不能穿过这个背景里的火山？
我必须干掉这火山
这尼玛真是科学
只需要踢一下火山然后就解决了
每一个象棋盘关的
终极目标就是干掉其他的怪兽
这个是摩杰拉和大章鱼
开什么玩笑
摩杰拉和章鱼一起
在所有的潜在的哥斯拉敌人中
他们选择了两个
根本就不是出自于哥斯拉电影的怪兽
我必须说《哥斯拉破坏神降临》出现了摩杰拉
《哥斯拉最后的战役》出现了章鱼怪
但那些电影都是在这
游戏出现后很长时间了才拍的
我还发现一个小技巧可以
直接干掉摩杰拉就是直接蹲下用尾巴扫
看吧 So easy（好简单）
怎么回事？这还有时间限制？
没错如果你打得太久了你就必须重新开始
敌人可以恢复一些能量就自己不行
其中最糟糕的部分就是
打败了摩杰拉和章鱼怪后到下一关的时候
你猜怎么着？
他俩好基友又回来了
每一个章节都要打这
两个基友不停地重复并且再加一个怪兽
这个是巴朗不明不白地来自于一部老电影
在哥斯拉电影里面出现过的杂鱼
和怪兽们的战斗选项非常的囧
你要干了这只怪兽吗？是
你想跟杰索拉干一场吗？
是你妹 它根本就不是敌人啊
有时候你不想和敌人干一场
选择No根本就没用
No!
我去！我说我不打！
有时候你想移动
怪兽就这样挡住了你的路
没错这里有个
怪兽我就是要跟它打
到后面敌人的
种类变得越来越多比我想象中的好
有"巴拉刚" 、有蛾怪兽（不是蛾怪）、"盖刚"还有"戈多"
但戈多在地图的最边缘，如果你运气好可以见到它
这个是钢铁哥斯拉
这就是我一直说想看到的
快了！快要打败钢铁哥斯啦了！
我去！你没！去你大爷的时间限制！
根本就没有倒数的数字
更多的像是直接拔掉了插头断电了
就像在说：你想赢吗？
好啊 你怎么不去吃屎呢
去你妹的这个脑残游戏玩家
就是这样游戏设计者作弊
整个游戏骗了了我的感情
我还没吐槽够
因为还有个后继的哥斯拉2
这个总该好一点了吧？
第一代玩起来让我伤了我的心
新的一代总该有点提升了吧
有时候做出点像屎一样的游戏就会有时间做好一点的屎游戏
这是神马？
这尼玛是哥斯拉游戏吗？
这就像是个模拟人生里面的哥斯拉突击游戏
你根本就玩不了哥斯拉
你是军队的某个高官
只不过就是移动一些格子
玩来玩去真像个无聊的飞行棋游戏
当进入了战斗模式后
这尼玛就是RPG游戏嘛
轮流攻击 不管你攻击还是
不攻击都要看上面的拉杆游戏机
没错 就是个垃圾的拉杆游戏机
我根本不知道它的工作原理
不过可以肯定的是
你永远都别想拉到三个同样图形的
你可能可以减少受到的伤害
但是怪兽不停地
获得HP 玩家想都别想
这游戏背景音乐真可怕
应该有一个选项把它关掉才是
要是你关掉了这音乐
所有的声音效果都关了
这是什么意思？
等于直接关了电视机声音
你觉得第一代很糟糕吗？
这尼玛就是在鄙视第一代游戏
这个游戏名字都不该叫哥斯拉2
就好象任天堂红白机的
忍者外传4实际上是个字谜游戏
你根本就不能把这个系列的
两款游戏当作同一类游戏看待
这不该改名叫
哥斯拉战略管理模拟装置
模拟哥斯拉吗 (sim 模拟人生）
好吧 我只能说这些了
让我们找找Gameboy上的哥斯拉
好吧 这看起来还比较可靠
这个游戏开始介绍游戏中会出现的角色
它们看起来都很不错
但是哥斯拉的头看起来有点怪怪的
就好象去毁灭了某个星球后回来了
让我们来看看游戏是怎么样的
你这是开哪国玩笑？
哥斯拉看起来像泡泡龙里面的怪兽
你走来走去 爬藤蔓 推石头
从嘴巴里面喷出一只拳击手套攻击怪物
他们怎么可以这样对待一只怪物之王
哥斯拉就好象穿着笨重的服装站在一跟弹簧高跳棒上
我才不要浪费我宝贵
时间在这屎一样的游戏上
引用著名的莎士比亚
最能总结这款游戏的一句话
"去你妹的"
Now let's move on to the Super Nintendo, Super Godzilla here.
Now there's the super, this means that it can not play.
But let's be serious.
Wow, 199X in ...
This would refer to the previous one, but now at least a little more specific date.
The graphics look good, such as that you would expect a Godzilla game.
But the gameplay is a completely different story.
You control Godzilla, designated by a blue dot on the bottom of the screen.
The top of the screen, but the spectacle is.
So Godzilla playing, would you want to destroy buildings right?
Well here, the buildings are suctioned out of energy.
It makes no sense. Godzilla destroyed buildings throughout his life,
The good thing is, as Mike Tyson would not be able to hit someone without causing damage to the hand.
If you encounter an enemy monster, the screen comes to fight.
Nah, it looks like what I was expecting a Godzilla game.
But no, not quite. Because I've never seen such fighting game.
Their frequency does not make sense at the bottom of the screen.
There are two stamina meter, which shows the fighting spirit.
He says: Keep your opponent low morale and hitting,
Godzilla attacking with open space and close it quickly.
So let me try to summarize.
Get close to the enemy, hit him, then quickly go back
and press left one or right to select the attack.
That's not what he did not say to press the damn left one or the right.
Why is it so damn hard to fight two monsters,
Why is it so hard to be like an Einstein Project.
I hate to say it, but I still like him better in the NES version.
Easy to understand how to play, but then gave up the Godzilla games.
If they can not release a good Super Nintendo, all hope was gone.
My wish is a traditional tournament-style game godzilla monsters.
Well my wish was fulfilled half.
My dreams Gozdilla game finished, but just launched in Japan.
Which means that the Super Famicom to play immediately.
they call it Godzilla ... (Whatever) finally play this good.
Today, there is not anything special, but I liked it.
Here most of the monsters in the movies, there are specific movements,
recognizable in the background, and the music is there.
That's fucking Godzillas.
But on the whole you will never forget,
Nintendo Power how to make fun of me with this game.
72 edition, May 1995.
"Coming Soon: Godzilla - Destroy All Monsters"
When I saw this card, the shit my pants.
Godzilla is a tournament? I can not wait to play!
More is not mentioned anywhere, nor is it found in the stores.
Only in Japan, but in Japan ...
15 years later, I'm still pulling up.
I just wanted a good Godzilla game, but the kid is gone, and I never got it.
But these days there are quite a Godzilla game
Godzilla - Destroy All Monsters Malee, Godzilla - Save the Earth,
Godzilla - Unleashed
It has been after my time there. I do not know anything about these.
Playsation 2? Something XBOX sucks.
But I'll give them a try.
Baaaszaaaa meeeeeeeeeg!!
Why were not these games when I was a kid?
Fuck, I was born too early!
Instead, I grew up with these pathetic shit asshole sucking with.
These games have sucked more than golyószopók!
Instead, I give Godzilla electroshock Meca-electric fuck of
These games are like crap to flow down from the smog monster huge asshole,
while they furiously absorb all of it while lying on a bed of nails,
push it all up in my ass!
While the withers into the hell of a fuck face!
Man! It's a fucked up! A rot! Fuck! Shit! Fuck ... Shit ...
Fuck, I just said it was just what my heart every curse ...
And you know, no more.
So one has to find a new curse.
I think I made it up.
This game, this game is a fucking ...
Oh Oh, aye. It's that bad.
- Sub by Dolfin - dolfinthereal@gmail.com  Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com